另一类重要的图像处理操作就是我们所说的二元运算。
Another important class of image processing operations are what we call diadic operations.
现在，diadic操作有两个输入参数和一个输出。正如我们讨论过的monadic
Now diadic operations have got two input arguments and one output. As we discussed for the monadic
情况下，我们有一个任意的功能;在这种情况下，它是两个输入变量的函数
case, we have an arbitrary function; in this case it is a function of two input variables
我们称之为x和y。所以它是f（x，y）。并且该功能应用于相应的
which we will call x and y. So it is f(x,y). And that function is applied to the corresponding
来自两个输入图像的像素，并将结果存放在相应的元素中
pixels from the two input images, and the result is deposited in the corresponding element
输出图像。所有三个图像必须完全相同，我们应用
of the output image. All three images have to be exactly the same size and we apply the
对两个输入图像中的每个像素具有相同的功能。
same function to every pixel in the two input images.
那么哪种函数对于二值图像处理有用呢？这是什么功能f
So what sort of functions are useful for diadic image processing? What is this function f
x和y？好吧，我们可以执行算术运算
of x and y? Well we could perform arithmetic, we could
将两个图像一起添加或者我们可以减去两个图像，或者我们可以将两个图像相乘。
add two images together or we could subtract two images, or we could multiply two images.
我们也可以执行更复杂的函数，例如取总和的平方根
We could also perform more complex functions like perhaps take the square root of the sum
广场。当涉及到实施其中一些时
of the squares. When it comes to implementing some of these
diadic操作，MATLAB的内置矢量化能力来帮助我们。
diadic operations, MATLAB’s inbuilt vectorization capacity comes to our aid.
所以，如果我要将两个矩阵一起添加，我使用plus运算符，
So if I was to add two matrices together, and I do that by using the plus operator,
MATLAB将做的是添加每个矩阵的相应元素，存放结果
what MATLAB will do is add the corresponding elements of each matrix, deposit the result
进入输出矩阵的相应元素。
into the corresponding element of the output matrix.
所有这些矩阵的大小都是完全相同的。
Once again all of these matrices are of exactly the same size.
所以我们可以使用任何MATLAB的算术运算符，我们也可以使用任何MATLAB
So we can use any of MATLAB’s arithmetic operators and we can also use any of MATLAB’s
内置逻辑运算符。如果我们使用逻辑运算符会发生什么
built-in logical operators. If we use the logical operators what happens
是使用该逻辑比较输入矩阵的相应元素
is that the corresponding elements of the input matrices are compared using that logic
运算符和结果，无论是真还是假，都存入相应的元素
operator and the result, either true or false, is deposited into the corresponding element
在输出矩阵中。现在你可能会注意到了这个
in the output matrix. Now you might notice here that amongst the
算术运算符有几个不寻常的。
arithmetic operators there are a couple of unusual ones.
一个是。*，这意味着将输入矩阵的相应元素相乘。
One is .* and that means multiply the corresponding elements of the input matrices together.
另一个是./，这意味着划分输入矩阵的相应元素。
And the other one is ./ which means divide the corresponding elements of the input matrices.
在MATLAB中，如果仅使用*运算符，那就是传统的矩阵乘法
In MATLAB if you use just the * operator, that is a traditional matrix multiplication
这是完全不同的。这里我们讨论的是逐个元素的乘法。
which is quite different. Here we are talking about multiplying element by element.
类似地，./表示输入矩阵中相应元素的元素划分，
Similarly, ./ means element wise division of corresponding elements in the input matrices,
其中/指的是乘以矩阵的倒数，这是完全不同的事情。
where / refers to multiplication by an inverse of a matrix, quite a different thing.
让我们来看一个diadic运算符的可能示例，并在此特定
Let’s have a look at a possible example of a diadic operator and in this particular
我们将看一下图像减法-一个图像减去另一个图像。
case we will look at image subtraction—one image minus another image.
所以这是一个从高角度向下俯视的交叉路口的图像。
So here is an image of an intersection taken from a high vantage point and looking down.
这是来自同一序列的另一帧-它实际上是序列中的第四帧。
And here is another frame from this same sequence—it is actually the fourth frame in the sequence.
这些图像看起来非常非常相似。交通流量不是很大
And these images look very, very similar to each other. The traffic is not moving very
很快。但如果我减去这两个图像，我得到了
quickly at all. But if I subtract these two images, I get
一个看起来像这样的图像。它所做的是它向我们展示了行踪
an image that looks like this. And what it has done is it has shown us whereabouts the
两个图像是不同的。它向我们展示了两幅图像之间的差异。什么
two images are different. It shows us the discrepancy between the two images. And what
我们可以看到这里有一些明亮的像素。所以这显示了很明显的下落
we can see is that there are some bright pixels up here. So this shows quite clearly whereabouts
这两个图像是不同的，我们可以看到差异主要在那一列
the two images are different and we can see that the difference is mostly in that column
交通，在框架中开始向下移动。
of traffic, which is beginning to move downward in the frame.
虽然图像看起来非常非常相似，但仅仅是通过区分它真的
Although the images look very, very similar, simply by taking the difference it really
突出显示图像发生变化的位置。
highlights where the change in the image has occurred.
但是，当我们减去像素值时，我们确实需要小心一点
But we do need to be a little bit careful when we subtract pixel values, particularly
如果它们是我们之前使用的无符号整数八种类型。
if they are of the unsigned integer eight type that we have used previously.
考虑这个例子。考虑第一帧中的像素值为55.相应的
Consider this example. Consider a pixel in frame one has got a value of 55. The corresponding
第二帧中的像素值为55.差异：显然为0。
pixel in frame two has got a value of 55. The difference: clearly 0.
现在在这种特殊情况下，第一帧中的像素值为60，它有点大
Now in this particular case the pixel in frame one has got a value of 60, it is a bit bigger
然后是第二帧中像素的值。差异显然是5。
then the value of the pixel in frame two. The difference is clearly of 5.
现在在这种情况下，当帧一个像素的值为55时，帧为两个像素
Now in this case when the frame one pixel has got a value of 55, the frame two pixel
得到的值为60，MATLAB将计算零差异，这是因为我们
has got a value of 60, MATLAB will compute a difference of zero and this is because we
正在减去无符号整数。根据定义，无符号整数不能为负数，
are subtracting unsigned integers. Unsigned integers cannot be negative by definition,
他们没有签名。因此，在这种情况下，我们将得到一个错误的结果。
they are unsigned. So in this case we are going to get an erroneous result.
解决它的方法是将图像转换为不同的数据类型;让他们离开
The way to get around it is to cast the images to a different data type; move them from being
无符号整数，可能是有符号整数，也可能是双精度浮点值。
unsigned integers, perhaps to being signed integers, or perhaps to being double precision floating point values.
让我们为此创造一个切实的例子。
Let’s create a tangible example of this.
我要创建一个相机，一个电影摄影机，这是一种特殊类型的对象打开
I am going to create a camera, a movie camera, which is a special type of object which opens
电影文件并将其作为单个灰度图像返回。
a movie file and returns the frames of that as individual grey scale images.
所以我创建了电影对象;它位于名为cam的工作空间中。这是一部电影
So I have created the movie object; it is in the workspace called cam. It is a movie
宾语。现在我要从那部电影中抓一帧。
object. And now I am going to grab one frame from that movie.
所以我将使用我们之前见过的抓取方法，我将抓住它
So I am going to use the grab method, which we have seen before and I am going to grab
电影中的第一帧。而我将从电影中抓出下一帧，
the first frame out of the movie. And I am going to grab the next frame out of the movie,
所以两个连续的帧。现在我将显示图像差异，我要去了
so two sequential frames. Now I am going to display the image difference and I am going
显示图像，该图像是图像1减去图像2的结果。
to display the image which is the result of image one minus image two.
在这里，我们看到一个灰度图像，它看起来有点不寻常，我们可以看到
And here we see a grey scale image and it looks a little bit unusual and we can see
这里有一些有趣的活动。im1减去im2的结果实际上是一个
some interesting activity around here. The result of im1 minus im2 is actually a
签字数量。图像1中的像素可以小于图像2中的像素。所以
signed quantity. The pixel in image one could be smaller then the pixel in image two. So
使用不同的颜色映射显示它很有用，我将使用该选项
it is useful to display this with a different colour map and I am going to use the option
在这里寄来。它将要做的是显示负像红色的像素
invsigned here. And what it is going to do is display pixels that are negative as red
和蓝色为正像素，背景为0，为白色。
and pixels that are positive as blue, and the background, where it is 0, is white.
所以让我们在这里放大图像的这一部分。我们可以看到的是一些红色像素
So let’s zoom in on this part of the image up here. And what we can see is some red pixels
和一些蓝色像素，这表明我们图像中的像素已经改变
and some blue pixels and this is showing us where the pixels in the image have changed
从一帧到下一帧。所以这就是场景中有动作的地方。
from one frame to the next. So this is where there is motion in the scene.
如果我们回去查看原始电影，我们可以看到这是交通的地方
If we go back and look at the original movie we can see that this is where the traffic
开始穿过十字路口。这些是场景中唯一的像素
starts to move across the intersection. These are the only pixels in the scene that are
改变。我们可以使用这种图像差异机制来确定哪些部分
changing. We can use this image difference mechanism to determine which parts of the
场景已经改变。
scene have been changed.
我们来讨论一个更复杂的图像处理操作。这就是所谓的
Let’s discuss a more sophisticated image processing operation. It is what is called
绿屏效果。我们想要做的是叠加这个抽象场景
the green screen effect. And what we want to do is to superimpose this abstract scene
一个帽子，一个球和一个梯子进入沙漠中的一个道路的场景。
of a hat, a ball and a ladder into the scene of a road in a desert.
我们想要做的是合并这两个图像，我们将使用这些信息来做到这一点
What we want to do is to merge these two images, and we are going to do that using the information
在顶部图像中，那些绿色的像素将被替换为
in the top image, where those pixels that are green are going to be substituted by the
底部图像的背景像素。绿屏效果被广泛使用
background pixels from the bottom image. The green screen effect is widely used in
电视制作，这是我拍摄其中一个介绍作品的形象
television production and here is an image of me filming one of the introductory pieces
对于MOOC。绿色背景中的所有像素都被a替换
for the MOOC. All of the pixels that are in the green background are substituted by a
照片和图形的数量等。
number of photographs and graphics and so on.
这种效果也被新闻阅读者，天气男人用在电视上。当我这样做时，它确实是
This effect is also used by newsreaders, weather men on TV. When I am doing this it is really
重要的是我不穿任何绿色的东西。例如，如果我穿了绿色
important that I don’t wear anything that is green. If, for instance, I wore a green
然后我的身体会消失，然后它会被背景照片取代。
shirt then my body would just disappear, and it would be replaced by the background photographs.
那么让我们来谈谈我们如何做绿屏效果。所以这是两个图像
So let’s talk about how we do the green screen effect. So here are the two images
再次。在顶部，我们有绿色背景和底部的抽象图像
again. In the top we have our abstract image against the green background and in the bottom
我们有想要将抽象图像叠加到的真实场景。
we have the real scene that we want to superimpose the abstract image into.
第一步是确定哪些像素是绿色的，我们通过做出两个决定来做到这一点
The first step is to determine which pixels are green and we do that by making two decisions
我们创建两个逻辑图像。顶部显示所有非绿色像素。
and we create two logical images. The top one shows all the pixels that are not green.
因此白色值表示相应的输入像素不是绿色。最底层的是
So white value means that the corresponding input pixel is not green. The bottom one is
与此相反：白色像素对应于输入图像中的绿色。这些图像
the opposite of that: the white pixels correspond to green in the input image. These images
是逻辑图像。像素只有值true或false。有时这些是
are logical images. The pixels have only got the value true or false. Sometimes these are
称为二进制图像，因为它们只有两个可能的值。有时他们被召唤
called binary images because they only have two possible values. Sometimes they are called
屏蔽图像，因为我们使用它们来屏蔽输入场景的特定区域。
mask images because we use them to mask out particular regions of the input scene.
然后，下一步是将掩模矩阵乘以原始输入图像。和
The next step then is to multiply the mask matrices by the original input images. And
我们在顶行的是一个图像，其中所有绿色像素都设置为黑色，
what we have in the top line is an image where all of the green pixels have been set to black,
剩下的像素是抽象对象。
and the remaining pixels are the abstract object.
我们对底部图像做同样的事情。我们将输入图像乘以掩码和
We do the same thing for the bottom image. We multiply the input image by the mask and
现在我们输入的图像中有一个洞。黑色像素对应于摘要
now we have the input image with a hole in it. The black pixels correspond to the abstract
宾语。请注意，我们已经使用了diadic操作
object. Notice that we have used the diadic operation
这里两次，在每种情况下将掩蔽的矩阵乘以原始彩色图像。
twice here, in each case to multiply a masked matrix by an original colour image.
最后一步是将这两个图像一起添加。这是另一个双向行动，
The last step then is to add these two images together. And that is yet another diadic operation,
然后我们剩下的是一个包含我们抽象对象的图像
and what we are left with then is an image which contains our abstract object against
沙漠场景的背景。
the background of a desert scene.